I don't know what they put in this product
M Caffeine The Perfume Body Lotion
This Perfume Body M Caffeine
so after seeing so many reviews I have
also ordered
so many products from M Caffeine Buy to get three let's
unbox it so I have tried these products for
three days I am
making the video after that so first of all is this
Choco Tinted Lip Balm which I got for free
it has very good packaging and the second
product is this Summer Braj Body Lotion let's try
it oh its smell is
exactly like that of a car those who have
problem of motion sickness should not use it at all.  The
lotion is very good but
I did not like its smell.  Second is this
10% magnesium lotion.  Its smell is just wow,
exactly like vanilla ice cream.  It
keeps the skin hydrated and smells
great too.  This turned out to be absolutely true.   The
third lotion is this sweet escape.  I
found it to be okay in terms of smell.  But the
texture of all the others is very good
and does not dry out the skin.  It is non-sticky
, paraben free and suits all skin types.